Guide to the Polly Shackleton papers, 1894-1997 MS2031
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Alphabetical files, 1975-1986; Series 8
  - Alfpha files F-P, 1975-1986; Series 8 Subseries 2
    - Filing, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Filing, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Finance & Revenue - John Wilson, 1983-1985; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Finance & Revenue Meeting, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Finance and Revenue - Tax State/Municiple Bond Income, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Finance and Revenue -- other, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Finance and Revenue Budget Amendment, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Finance and Revenue Committee Meeting, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Finance and Revenue Committee Meeting, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Finance and Revenue Hearing - 4-303 GW Revenue Bonds, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Finance and Revenue Hearing - Oversight Board on E & R, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Frank Smith, 1986; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 38)
    - Friendship Heights Cafe, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Friendship Heights Cafe, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Friendship Heights Cafe, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Friendship Postal Station, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - G-64 "Drinking by Minors Enforcement Act", 1983-1985; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - G54 "Vacant Property Hazard Elimination Enforcement Act", 1983-1985; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Gambling - Lotteries, etc., 1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Gardens - Glover Park Community Garden, 1982-1985; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Georgetown - Waterfront & General, 1979-1985; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Georgetown Business & Professional Association, 1984; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Georgetown Day School - Construction, 1985; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Georgetown Hoyas Basketball Team Recognition Resolution of 1984, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Georgetown Sub-Division, 1967-1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Georgetown University, 1980-1984; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Georgetowner, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Gertrude Stein Democratics Club (Gay Activists Alliance), 1976-1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Goals and Policies, 1976-1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Goddard Cafe, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Gray Panthers, 1976-1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Hammond Court Tenants Association, 1979; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Handicapped Parking, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Hatch Act, 1975-1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Health, 1974-1975; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Health Planning Advisory Committee (HPAC), 1975; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Hillandale Development Corporation, 1979-1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 21a, Folder 7)
    - Hillcrest Children's Center, 1976; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Historic District Protection Act of 1978, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Historic Georgetown Properties, 1976; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Historic Preservation, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Historic Preservation, 1985; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Hollow Point Bullet Act, 1977; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Home Rule DC, 1980-1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Homosexuality - Employment Opportunity Gay Pride Week, 1977; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Housing Bill 3-222, 1980-1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Housing Finance Agency Board of Directors, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - I-66 (Interstate Highway), 1975-1979; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - I-66 Right Turn on Red, 1976-1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - ILH, 1978-1984; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 21a, Folder 12)
    - Inabel Burns Lindsay Recognition Resolution of 1983, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Industrial Revenue Bonds, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Initiative #7, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - International Senior Citizens Week Resolution, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Interns, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 21a, Folder 10)
    - Invitations, 1980; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Invitations (1 of 2), 1979; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Invitations (2 of 2), 1979; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Invitations (2), 1977; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Iona House, 1976-1986; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 21a, Folder 11)
    - Iona House Senior Service Center 10th A. Recy Res.", 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Issues, 1978-1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Italian Embassy, 1977; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - "J.C. Hayward Recognition Resolution", 1984; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Job Application - Stephen Lewis Forestnzer, 1985; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Job Corps, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Joel Joseph - Candidate for Ward 3, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 21a, Folder 8)
    - Joint Committee on Landmarks, 1976; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Jr. League of Washington 1, 1982-1985; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Jr. League of Washington 2, 1979-1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Jr. League of Washington 3, 1975-1979; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - "Judith H. Miller Recognition Resolution of 1985", Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Kennedy Center Bus Service, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Landlord-Tenant, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Lead Poisons, 1977; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - League of Women Voters 1, 1978-1986; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - League of Women Voters 2, 1974-1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Legal Assistance, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Legislataion Merit Personnel Act, 1980; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Legislation Introduced by Polly, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Legislative Session, 1979-1980; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Legislative Sessions, COW Sessions, Bill Introduced by PS-Council Pd4, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Legislative Summaries, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Licensing and Inspection, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - List "F", 1980; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - List ANC List, 1981 November 03; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - List Apartments Bdge and Misc - Condos, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - List-Contributors - Keeffe Campaign, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - List-Keeffe Campaign Committee, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - List-Polly-ALPHA, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - List-Shackleton Re-Election Committee, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Lists - League of Women Voters, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Lists - PTA Presidents W.3, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Lists-BY Precincts PS 1978 Campaign, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Lists-Democratic Committee Ward 3, 1979-1980; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Lists-For Precinct Workers, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Litter Free Washington Committee, 1984-1985; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Looks like names of voters, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Lorton, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - "Mae B. Philips 90th Birthday Celebration", 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Mailing Lists and Labels, 1976-1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Marijuana Reform Law, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Mary Lampson, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Massage Parlors, 1976; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - McLean Gardens, 1975-1985; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 21a, Folder 3)
    - McLean Gardens Development Project, 1975-1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 21a, Folder 6)
    - Media - General, 1975-1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Media List, 1980; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Memos - To/From - Director, Department of Human Resources, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Mental Health (Area A), Undated; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 21a, Folder 4)
    - Metro Fare Increase Hearing, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Metro Garage, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Metro Hearing - Friendship Heights Shuttle Bus, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Metro-D2 etc, 1986; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Metro-General, 1983-1984; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Metrobus Proposed Cuts on Connecticut Ave. Hearing, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Meyer Foundation, 1985-1986; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, 1975-1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Mondale, 1984; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Motorized Bicycle Act, 1976; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - "Mr/Mrs Wilbur Warren Recognition Resolution", 1985; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Municipal Planning Office, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - NAACP (Legal Defense and Educational Fund), 1985-1986; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Nathanson, Jim, 1986; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 21a, Folder 5)
    - National Airport, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - National Association of Social Workers, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - National Capital Planning Commission, 1984; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - National Commission on Confidentiality of Health Records Inc., 1977-1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - National League of Cities, 1976; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Newsletter 1, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Newsletter 2, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Newsletter 3, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper Articles on Nursing Homes, 1986; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Noise, 1977-1979; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Non-Smokers Rights Bill, 1978-1979; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Northwest Current, 1975-1977; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 21a, Folder 1)
    - NPEC Briefing, 1977-1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Nuclear Freeze, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Nurse Practice Act Bill 2-261, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Office Administration, 1975-1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Office of the Corporation Counsel, 1984; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Office on Aging, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Office on Aging, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Official Speeches, 1980; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Official Speeches, 1977; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Official Speeches Shackleton, 1979; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Official Speeches Shackleton, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - Official Speeches Shackleton, 1976; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Official Statements - Shackleton, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Official Statements - Shackleton, 1980; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Official Statements - Shackleton, 1979; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Official Statements - Shackleton, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Official Statements - Shackleton, 1977; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Official Statements - Shackleton, 1976; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Official Statements - Shackleton, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Official Statements by PS, 1984; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Official Statements Shackleton, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Ordway Gardens, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - PADCO, 1978-1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Parking Tax, 1976; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Party April 4 Receipts, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Party April 4 Receipts, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Pay Raise Legislation, 1980; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Pay Raise Proposals, Legislation, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - People's Counsel, 1979-1986; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - People's Counsel 2, 1975-1979; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Peoples Counsel Brain Lederer/Dorse-1, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - PEPCO, 1983-1985; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Personnel, 1979; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Personnel, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Personnel, 1979-1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Personnel, 1975-1986; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Petition Drive, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Petty Cash Receipts Finance (Campaign), Undated; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Planning, 1974-1975; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Playgrounds, 1984; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 21b, Folder 2)
    - Police Employee Contracts, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Police Officer Outside Employment, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Politics, 1984; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Polly - Biographical Material, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 21a, Folder 13)
    - Polly - correspondence, 1975-1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 21b, Folder 1)
    - Polly Shackleton Co-Chairs Meeting, 1984; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Preservation of Historic Buildings, 1974-1985; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - President Pro Tempore Nadine Winter, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - Press Clippings (by date), 1974-1975; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - Press Contacts, 1975-1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - Press Releases, 1982-1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Press Releases - Shackleton, 1977; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Press Releases - Shackleton, 1976; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Press Releases - Shackleton, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Pricing of Prescription Drugs, 1975-1976; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - PRIDE Bill, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Pride Bill, 1978-1979; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Primary Election, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Program of Policy Studies - GWU, 1977; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Proposed Hotel - Wisconsin Ave. and Resevoir, 1984-1985; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Proposed Legislation, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Propriety School Requirements, 1981-1982; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - PS Bills - Sponsor, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - PSCA Meeting, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Public Accountants, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Public Hearing "District of Columbia Unemployment Compensation Act Amendment of 1977", Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Public Hearing on Bill 3-47 Location of Chanceries Amendment of 1979, Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Public Oversight Hearing on Tax Collection and Billing Practices and Procedures in the Department of FInance and Revenue, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Public Property Elimination Act, 1977; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Public Safety, 1974; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Public Service Commission, 1979; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Public Services & Cable Television Kane, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Alpha files Q-Z, numerical, 1975-1986; Series 8 Subseries 3
    - Questionnaires, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 21b, Folder 3)
    - Radio and TV, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - "Real Property Wet Settlement Act", 1984-1986; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Re-election Committee, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Re-Election Postcards, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Re-Election Postcards, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Real Estate General 1, 1983-1984; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Real Estate General 2, 1982-1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Real Estate General 3, 1980-1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Real Estate Property Tax Rate, 1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Recommendations for Positions (1 of 23), 1984-1986; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Recommendations for Positions (2 of 23), 1984; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Recommendations for Positions (3 of 23), 1984; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Recommendations for Positions (4 of 23), 1983-1984; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Recommendations for Positions (5 of 23), 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Recommendations for Positions (6 of 23), 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Recommendations for Positions (7 of 23), 1981-1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Recommendations for Positions (8 of 23), 1980-1981; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Recommendations for Positions (9 of 23), 1980; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Recommendations for Positions (10 of 23), 1979-1980; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Recommendations for Positions (11 of 23), 1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Recommendations for Positions (12 of 23), 1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Recommendations for Positions (13 of 23), 1978-1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Recommendations for Positions (14 of 23), 1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Recommendations for Positions (15 of 23), 1977-1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Recommendations for Positions (16 of 23), 1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Recommendations for Positions (17 of 23), 1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Recommendations for Positions (18 of 23), 1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Recommendations for Positions (19 of 23), 1976; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Recommendations for Positions (20 of 23), 1976; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Recommendations for Positions (21 of 23), 1975-1976; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Recommendations for Positions (22 of 23), 1975; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Recommendations for Positions (23 of 23), 1975; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Recreation, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Redistricting - Council Memoranda/Press Re-Leases, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Redskin Ticket List, 1983-1986; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Regulations, 1973-1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Rent Control - Correspondence & Legislation, 1980; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Rent Control 1, 1980-1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Rent Control 2, 1979-1980; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Rent Control 3, 1975-1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Rent Subsidy Program, 1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Rental Accommodations, 1975-1981; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Rented Housing Committee, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Resolutions (1), 1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Resolutions (2), 1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Retirement Board, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Retirement Reform Act Amendments, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Returnable Bottle Bill, 1975-1976; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Rhodes Tavern, 1982-1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Rosedale, 1976-1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Rountable on PR 4-189, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Russian Embassy, 1974-1976; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - SAC-8 (1 of 3), 1976-1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - SAC-8 (2 of 3), 1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - SAC-8 (3 of 3), 1975-1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Safeway Rezoning, 1977; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Sales Tax, 1975-1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - School Board, 1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - School Board - Campaign Literature, 1981; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - School Ward (1 of 8), 1985-1986; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - School Ward (2 of 8), 1985; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - School Ward (3 of 8), 1984; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - School Ward (4 of 8), 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - School Ward (5 of 8), 1982-1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - School Ward (6 of 8), 1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - School Ward (7 of 8), 1980-1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - School Ward (8 of 8), 1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Schools-Mail from Children (1 of 6), 1982-1985; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Schools-Mail from Children (2 of 6), 1979-1982; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Schools-Mail from Children (3 of 6), 1978-1979; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Schools-Mail from Children (4 of 6), 1977-1978; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Schools-Mail from Children (5 of 6), 1976; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Schools-Mail from Children (6 of 6), 1975-1976; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Schwartz, 1986; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Second District Police - Captain Canfield, 1983; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 21b, Folder 4)
    - Senate District Committee, 1975; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Senior Citizens Discount Program, 1976; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Senior Citizens of Today and Tomorrow, 1985; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 17)